<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Machine learning (ML) has established itself as the dominant and most successful paradigm for artificial intelligence (AI). A key strength of ML over earlier (symbolic, logic and rule-based) approaches to AI, is its ability to infer useful features or representations of often very high-dimensional observations in an automated, data-driven way. However, in doing so, it generally only leverages statistical information (e.g., correlations present in a training set) and consequently struggles at tasks such as knowledge transfer, systematic generalization, or planning, which are thought to require higher-order cognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/accepted-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/accepted-papers/</guid>
      <description>Accepted Papers Orals Multivariable Causal Discovery with General Nonlinear Relationships
Patrik Reizinger, Yash Sharma, Matthias Bethge, Bernhard Schölkopf, Ferenc Huszár, Wieland Brendel
Abstraction between Structural Causal Models: A Review of Definitions and Properties Fabio Massimo Zennaro
Partial Disentanglement via Mechanism Sparsity
Sebastien Lachapelle, Simon Lacoste-Julien
Causal Class Activation Maps for Weakly-Supervised Semantic Segmentation
Yiping Wang
Posters A Meta-Reinforcement Learning Algorithm for Causal Discovery
Andreas W.M. Sauter, Erman Acar, Vincent Francois-Lavet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/call-for-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/call-for-papers/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers We welcome submissions related to any aspects of CRL, including but not limited to:
Learning latent (structural) causal models &amp;amp; structured (deep) generative models Interventional representations, causal digital twins &amp;amp; structured (causal) world models Post-hoc extraction of causal relations from (deep) generative models Self-supervised causal representation learning Multi-environment &amp;amp; multi-view causal representation learning Micro vs. macro/coarse-grained/multi-level causal systems Identifiable representation learning &amp;amp; nonlinear ICA Uncertainty quantification in (causal) representation learning Group-theoretic &amp;amp; symmetry-based views on disentanglement Invariance &amp;amp; equivariance in representation learning Interdisciplinary perspectives on causal representation learning, including from cognitive science, psychology, (computational) neuroscience or philosophy Real-world applications of causal representation learning, including in biology, medical sciences, or robotics Submissions should present novel, unpublished work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Committee</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/organizers/</guid>
      <description>Organizers Julius von Kügelgen Luigi Gresele Francesco Locatello Sara Magliacane Nan Rosemary Ke Yixin Wang Yoshua Bengio Reviewers Alexander Hägele, ETH Zürich
Biwei Huang, Carnegie Mellon University
Bohdan Kivva, University of Chicago
Bryon Aragam, University of Chicago
Chandler Squires, Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Cian Eastwood, University of Edinburgh
Daniel Malinsky, Johns Hopkins University
Davide Talon, Università degli Studi di Genova, Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia
Dhanya Sridhar, Université de Montréal and Mila-Quebec AI Institute</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Committee</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/program-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/program-committee/</guid>
      <description>Program Committee Organizers Julius von Kügelgen Luigi Gresele Francesco Locatello Sara Magliacane Nan Rosemary Ke Yixin Wang Yoshua Bengio Reviewers Alexander Hägele, ETH Zürich
Biwei Huang, Carnegie Mellon University
Bohdan Kivva, University of Chicago
Bryon Aragam, University of Chicago
Chandler Squires, Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Cian Eastwood, University of Edinburgh
Daniel Malinsky, Johns Hopkins University
Davide Talon, Università degli Studi di Genova, Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia
Dhanya Sridhar, Université de Montréal and Mila-Quebec AI Institute</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/selected-references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/selected-references/</guid>
      <description>Selected References The following is a non-exhaustive list of selected references related to the topics of the workshop, compiled before announcing the call for papers.
Kosoy, E., Liu, A., Collins, J.L., Chan, D., Hamrick, J.B., Ke, N.R., Huang, S., Kaufmann, B., Canny, J. &amp;amp; Gopnik, A. Learning Causal Overhypotheses through Exploration in Children and Computational Models. Conference on Causal Learning and Reasoning, 2022.
Ahuja, K., Hartford, J., &amp;amp; Bengio, Y. Properties from Mechanisms: An Equivariance Perspective on Identifiable Representation Learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/program/</guid>
      <description>Invited Speakers Bernhard Schölkopf Alison Gopnik Aapo Hyvärinen Caroline Uhler Gemma Moran Sander Beckers Phillip Lippe Anirudh Goyal Preliminary Schedule Legend: contributed · invited · break Time Program 08:50 - 09:00 Introductory remarks 09:00 - 10:00 Keynote talks (2 x 30 min) 10:00 - 10:30 Coffee break 10:30 - 11:00 Contributed talks (2 x 15 min) 11:00 - 12:00 Invited talks (2 x 30 min) 12:00 - 13:00 Poster session 1 13:00 - 14:00 Lunch break 14:00 - 15:00 Invited talks (2 x 30 min) 15:00 - 15:15 Contributed talk (15 min) 15:15 - 15:45 Coffee break 15:45 - 16:00 Contributed talk (15 min) 16:00 - 17:00 Keynote talks (2 x 30 min) 17:00 - 18:00 Poster session 2 All times according to Central European Summer Time (CEST).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Invited Speakers Bernhard Schölkopf Alison Gopnik Aapo Hyvärinen Caroline Uhler Gemma Moran Sander Beckers Phillip Lippe Anirudh Goyal Preliminary Schedule Legend: contributed · invited · break Time Program 08:50 - 09:00 Introductory remarks 09:00 - 10:00 Keynote talks (2 x 30 min) 10:00 - 10:30 Coffee break 10:30 - 11:00 Contributed talks (2 x 15 min) 11:00 - 12:00 Invited talks (2 x 30 min) 12:00 - 13:00 Poster session 1 13:00 - 14:00 Lunch break 14:00 - 15:00 Invited talks (2 x 30 min) 15:00 - 15:15 Contributed talk (15 min) 15:15 - 15:45 Coffee break 15:45 - 16:00 Contributed talk (15 min) 16:00 - 17:00 Keynote talks (2 x 30 min) 17:00 - 18:00 Poster session 2 All times according to Central European Summer Time (CEST).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
