<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About the workshop Machine learning (ML) has established itself as the dominant and most successful paradigm for artificial intelligence (AI). A key strength of ML over earlier (symbolic, logic and rule-based) approaches to AI, is its ability to infer useful features or representations of often very high-dimensional observations in an automated, data-driven way. However, in doing so, it generally only leverages statistical information (e.g., correlations present in a training set) and consequently struggles at tasks such as knowledge transfer, systematic generalization, or planning, which are thought to require higher-order cognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/accepted-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/accepted-papers/</guid>
      <description>Accepted Papers Orals Multivariable Causal Discovery with General Nonlinear Relationships
Patrik Reizinger, Yash Sharma, Matthias Bethge, Bernhard Schölkopf, Ferenc Huszár, Wieland Brendel
Abstraction between Structural Causal Models: A Review of Definitions and Properties Fabio Massimo Zennaro
Partial Disentanglement via Mechanism Sparsity
Sebastien Lachapelle, Simon Lacoste-Julien
Causal Class Activation Maps for Weakly-Supervised Semantic Segmentation
Yiping Wang
Posters A Meta-Reinforcement Learning Algorithm for Causal Discovery
Andreas W.M. Sauter, Erman Acar, Vincent Francois-Lavet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/call-for-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/call-for-papers/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers We welcome submissions related to any aspects of CRL, including but not limited to:
Learning latent (structural) causal models &amp;amp; structured (deep) generative models Interventional representations, causal digital twins &amp;amp; structured (causal) world models Post-hoc extraction of causal relations from (deep) generative models Self-supervised causal representation learning Multi-environment &amp;amp; multi-view causal representation learning Micro vs. macro/coarse-grained/multi-level causal systems Identifiable representation learning &amp;amp; nonlinear ICA Uncertainty quantification in (causal) representation learning Group-theoretic &amp;amp; symmetry-based views on disentanglement Invariance &amp;amp; equivariance in representation learning Interdisciplinary perspectives on causal representation learning, including from cognitive science, psychology, (computational) neuroscience or philosophy Real-world applications of causal representation learning, including in biology, medical sciences, or robotics Submissions should present novel, unpublished work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formatting Instructions</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/formatting-instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/formatting-instructions/</guid>
      <description>Formatting Instructions Style &amp;amp; Author Instructions Submissions should be formatted using the UAI latex template and formatting instructions. Papers must be submitted as a PDF file and should be 4-6 pages in length, including all main results, figures, and tables. Appendices containing additional details are allowed, but reviewers are not expected to take this into account.
Submission Link https://openreview.net/group?id=auai.org/UAI/2022/Workshop/CRL
Camera-Ready Revisions Camera-Ready revisions are now enabled in OpenReview. While the workshop has no official proceedings, we strongly encourage you to submit a revised &amp;ldquo;camera-ready&amp;rdquo; version taking reviewers&amp;rsquo; comments and suggestions into account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Dates</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/dates/</guid>
      <description>Important Dates Paper submission deadline: June 6, 2022, 23:59 AoE Notification to authors: July 5, 2022, 23:59 AoE Camera-ready version: August 17, 2022, 23:59 AoE Workshop Date: August 5, 2022 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited Speakers</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/invited-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/invited-speakers/</guid>
      <description>Invited Speakers Bernhard Schölkopf Alison Gopnik Aapo Hyvärinen Caroline Uhler Gemma Moran Sander Beckers Phillip Lippe Anirudh Goyal </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisers</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/organisers-reviewers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/organisers-reviewers/</guid>
      <description>Organisers Julius von Kügelgen Luigi Gresele Francesco Locatello Sara Magliacane Nan Rosemary Ke Yixin Wang Yoshua Bengio Reviewers Adam Li, Columbia University
Alexander Hägele, ETHZ - ETH Zurich
Biwei Huang, Carnegie Mellon University
Bohdan Kivva, University of Chicago
Bryon Aragam, University of Chicago
Chandler Squires, Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Cian Eastwood, University of Edinburgh
Daniel Malinsky, Johns Hopkins University
Davide Talon, Università degli Studi di Genova, Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewers</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/reviewers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/reviewers/</guid>
      <description>Reviewers Adam Li, Columbia University
Alexander Hägele, ETHZ - ETH Zurich
Biwei Huang, Carnegie Mellon University
Bohdan Kivva, University of Chicago
Bryon Aragam, University of Chicago
Chandler Squires, Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Cian Eastwood, University of Edinburgh
Daniel Malinsky, Johns Hopkins University
Davide Talon, Università degli Studi di Genova, Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia
Dhanya Sridhar, Université de Montréal and Mila-Quebec AI Institute
Furui Liu, Huawei Technologies Ltd.
Gargi Balasubramaniam, University of Illinois, Urbana Champaign</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule and Format</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/schedule-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/schedule-format/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Schedule Legend: contributed · invited · break Time Program Format 09:00 - 09:30 Introductory remarks In-person 09:30 - 10:00 Aapo Hyvärinen - &#34;Causal Discovery and Latent-Variable Models&#34; Virtual (live) 10:00 - 10:30 Coffee break - 10:30 - 10:45 Sebastien Lachapelle - “Partial Disentanglement via Mechanism Sparsity” In-person 10:45 - 11:00 Patrik Reizinger - “Multivariable Causal Discovery with General Nonlinear Relationships” In-person 11:00 - 11:30 Phillip Lippe - &#34;Learning Causal Variables from Temporal Sequences with Interventions&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides and Recording</title>
      <link>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/slides-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crl-uai-2022.github.io/slides-recording/</guid>
      <description>Slides Slides from the speakers can be downloaded at the links below.
Aapo Hyvärinen Sebastien Lachapelle Patrik Reizinger Phillip Lippe Anirudh Goyal Sander Beckers Caroline Uhler Fabio Massimo Zennaro Yiping Wang Bernhard Schölkopf (Coming soon) Gemma Moran Recording This is a recording of talks that took place in the second part of the workshop (after the lunch break); recordings of the first part of the workshop are unfortunately not available.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
